

SKILLS

- Web Design
- Design Thinking
- Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

EDUCATION

HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL

New Model Junior College 2015- 2016

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION

Bharati Vidyapeeth University 2017 - 2021

HUZAIFA NADAF

PROFILE

I am a qualified web developer with website design. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail. My goal is to become associated with a company where I can utilize my skills and gain further experience while enhancing the company's productivity and reputation.

EXPERIENCE

SALES EXECUTIVE (PART - TIME)

Really Great Company

2023 - Present

- Customised service offerings to accommodate consumer needs.
- Showcased product features and benefits to drive sales.
- Closed large sales to exceed quota and align with company targets.

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT EXECUTIVE

Ideametrics Pvt Ltd

2022 - 2023

- Developed and implemented strategic business plans and marketin strategies.
- Cold and warm called new and existing accounts per day.
- Developed business growth plans by identifying key clients, critical targets and priority service lines.